(Penny:)So are you and Leonard working
on an experiment together?
- Yeah, we are.
- We're examining the radiation levels...
(Leonard:)...of photomultiplier tubes
for a new dark-matter detector.
(Penny:)Sweetie, sweetie, Dave was talking.
(Penny:)You know, I love science.
- Since when?
- Since always.
(Penny:)Call me a geek, but I am just nuts
for the whole subatomic-particle thing.
DAVID: The last thing
I would ever call you is a geek.
Oh, well, that's what I am.
Queen of the nerds.
Hey, if you'd like, I could show you
the lab we're working in.
(David:)We've got some cool toys, you know.
Lasers and stuff.
(Penny:)You know, I have always wanted to see
a big science lab.
- Since when?
- Since always.
(David:)Leonard, are you okay here?
(Leonard:)- Yeah, I guess.
- How about we go see it now?
(David:)Afterwards, we take the bike up the coast,
we grab a bite to eat?
Um, yeah. Yeah, that sounds great.
Let me just get my jacket.
[DOOR CLOSES]
(David:)Boy, she'll do, huh?
(Leonard:)Yeah, if you like that type.